hypertracker.com 2017-12-14

# HyperTracker.com

GetResponse realizes that you care how your information is processed and shared, and we appreciate your trust in us to do that carefully and sensibly. This document describes our Privacy Policy. By visiting our website and using our HyperTracker Service, you are accepting and consenting to the practices described in this Privacy Policy. 

Any personal information provided or acquired by GetResponse is controlled primarily by the GetResponse Company, Balladyny 26, 81-524 Gdynia, Poland, hereinafter referred to as "GetResponse". 

We believe it is important to you, our Customer, to know how we treat the information about you, which we receive during your visits to our site and/or using our Service. This Privacy Policy is designed to assist you in understanding how we collect, disclose, and safeguard the aggregate information we receive when you visit and browse our website. We encourage you to take the time to read this Privacy Policy as well as those of any other sites you visit, whether through a link on that site or otherwise. 

GetResponse undertakes all commercially reasonable endeavors to keep all disclosed personal information secure. Information collected through tracking and registration will not be shared or sold to third parties for any purpose without your express consent, except as provided in this Privacy Policy, or in a contract between GetResponse and you, our valuable Customer. 

When you visit our website, we receive and may collect two types of information: (1) site use information and cookies, and (2) personal information you knowingly choose to disclose, which is collected on individual basis. 

Information We Collect 

GetResponse collects personal information from Customers who visit this Site and register with our HyperTracker Service. When the Customers registers with our HyperTracker Service, we require: (i) username, (ii) password, (iii) email address, (iv) first and last name, (v) zip code, (vi) country and (vii) billing information such as billing address and credit card number (ix) tax id number. We may also ask Customers to provide additional personal information such as (i) company name, (ii) title, (iii) education institution and (iv) other company and (v) personal details that the Customer may opt out of by not entering data when asked. We use the Customer’s registration information to authenticate users and provide access to HyperTracker Service. We also use the email addresses used in the registration information to communicate with our Customers. From time to time, GetResponse may contact you via email to notify you of changes to its Service, scheduled maintenance, information about GetResponse and promotional materials from GetResponse. 

GetResponse shall use all reasonable endeavors to give you free access to your personal information in an appropriate scope. You may change or delete your personally identifiable information at any time by [contacting us](http://hypertracker.cs.getresponse.com/ModSupportTicket/CreateTicket/visitor) and clearly indicating that you wish to change or deactivate and delete such information. 

Other than as disclosed in this Privacy Policy, at no time will GetResponse share, rent or sell your identifiable personal information to any third parties without your express consent. 

You agree and acknowledge that your information collected through this Site and related Services or in connection with the HyperTracker Service may be transferred across national boundaries and stored and processed in any of the countries around the world in which GetResponse maintains offices, including the United State 

Passwords 

Your GetResponse and HyperTracker account information, your username, password and a customer’s profile are password-protected so that you have secure access to entering and editing personal data. It is the user's responsibility to protect the security of their password. Access to HyperTracker Service is protected by a unique username and password that is known to you only. GetResponse has designed internal security processes that encrypt Customer’s password to protect it from being divulged or accessed by anyone other than you. Neither GetResponse employees nor any of its contractors can obtain or access your password. Neither GetResponse employees or nor any of its contractors will ask you for your password via mail, email, telephone or in any other unsolicited manner. 

Site Use Information 

Our servers automatically collect site use information, each time you visit our site. 

The site use information includes, but is not limited to, the following: the domain names, operating system in use (e.g. Macintosh, Windows), browser (e.g. Netscape, Internet Explorer) and version, the website which referred you to us, and other similar information. This information may be aggregated to measure the number of visits, average time spent on our website, pages viewed, time and date of visits, and other similar information. We may use and disclose site use information, for example, to measure the use of our website, improve the content, explain the utility of our website and services we provide, and to extend their functionality. 

Similar to other commercial websites, the technology called "cookies" may be used to provide you with tailored information. A cookie is a small piece of data that a website can send to your browser, which may then be stored on your hard drive, so we can recognize you when you return. You may be able to set your browser to notify you when you receive a cookie. Our cookies collect general information that enhances our ability to serve you and measure the utility of our website. 

Information we collect may be used to enhance your use of our website, and to provide you with a service that you ordered, arrange the website in the most customer friendly way, communicate special offers and featured items, and/or respond to your questions and suggestions. 

In the case of an agreement, personal information includes data that identifies you as the specific individual, i.e. your name, email address, phone number, geographical address, and/or company name and company address. This information is used to complete the account application process, Customer's information request, and/or to verify the validity of the request, and to process payment. 

We will use this information solely for performing Services and processing payments for those Services that you ordered. 

**GetResponse collects only personal information that you choose to provide voluntarily registering to our HyperTracker Service. GetResponse shall advise you which information is mandatory to provide and what you do not have to enclose.**

Mailing Policy 

When you send us an email, we use your email address to thank you for your comment and/or reply to your question, and we will store your communication and our reply for any future correspondence. Beyond our initial reply, we will never use your email address to send you any unsolicited message or information, nor will we share it with or sell it to anyone else for such use. 

When you accept to receive information about our Services, promotions and/or new offers, we use your email address and any other information you give us to provide you with the requested information and/or Services, until you ask us to stop (using the 'unsubscribe' instructions provided with each email, and/or on the site where you signed up, and/or as we otherwise provide). 

When you request information or other Services from us, we use your email address and any other information you give us to provide you with the information and/or other Services that you requested, until you ask us to stop (using the 'unsubscribe' instructions provided with each email, and/or on the site where you signed up, and/or as we otherwise provide), or until the information or Service is no longer available. 

We will never use your email address or other information to provide you with any unsolicited messages or information (unless that is part of the Service you request), nor will we share it with or sell, rent or lease it to any third party for such use. 

Your Recipient's Private Information Policy 

GetResponse recognizes the importance of respecting the privacy of those who decided to entrust their sensitive information with you. We assure to make every effort to safeguard their security. GetResponse will never use the information about the customers you collect within our services to send any unsolicited messages or information, nor will we share it with or sell it to anyone else for such use. 

Information Security 

We believe that keeping personal information secure is one of our most significant responsibilities. 

We restrict access to personal information about you to those employees and others who need to know that information to assist us in our business, or to provide products or Services to you. We safeguard personal information, according to the established security standards and procedures, by maintaining physical, electronic, and procedural safeguards to the personal data information. 

When we request our Customers to enter sensitive information, such as their name, geographical address, email address, and a credit card number, it is encrypted and protected with the best encryption software in the industry, SSL, and processed through a reputable payment processor [PayLane](http://www.paylane.com/). While on the secure page, such as our order form, the lock icon at the bottom of web browsers, e.g. Mozilla Firefox or Microsoft Internet Explorer, becomes locked, as opposed to unlocked or open, when you are just 'surfing'. 

All of our Customers' information, not just the sensitive information mentioned above, is restricted in our offices. Only employees who need the information to perform a specific job (e.g. our billing clerk or a Customer Service Representative) are personally granted access to. 

Security 

GetResponse stores its servers in a highly secure server environment, with surveillance and support to prevent unauthorized access and data security. 

We cannot guarantee the security of your data while it is being transmitted over the Internet and through servers that are out of our control. We strive to protect your personal information but GetResponse cannot ensure or warrant the security of any information you transmit to our website or Services. Any data transmissions you make over the Internet are done so at your own risk. Once we receive the data transmission, we make our best efforts to ensure its security and privacy on our systems.
